<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>1.4.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Pallet Autoload Specialization</en>
        <de>Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung</de>
        <ru>Автопогрузка</ru>
        <it>Specializzazione Caricamento Automatico Pallet</it>
        <fr>Spécialisation De Chargement Automatique De Palettes</fr>
        <es>Especialización Carga Automática Palés</es>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Base Mod for using Mods with Pallet Autoload Specialization

An example of how to use in your own mod you will find in the Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Currently only default Euro pallets, liquidTanks, bigbag pallets and Round Bales are possible, more will follow.

How to use:
Drive next to the pallets and then with [R] you can start the loading process.
Make sure you have selected the correct pallet type.
The pallets are then as loaded by hand on the loading area. 
Fasten with straps before you drive, otherwise it fell of.
You can choose the unloading side and unload it.

Instructions for build in and help you will find on the <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog 1.0.1.0
- Error for Cotton Round Bales on Dedi solved
- small changed loading/unloading behavior to work against the wrong display of the Engine in Dedi

Changelog 1.2.0.0
- Missing translations added for shop.
- Change bindings to be configurable bindings for minimizing double usage.
- Sapling pallets could now be loaded with the Euro pallet setting. 
- New loading type for oversized Europallets like the ones from KsAG or Schaumann (smaller loading capacity).
- Change loading to load everything automatic what is in range with one time pressing [R].
- Pioneer pallet is now loadable with the oversized setting.

Changelog 1.2.1.0
- Improved translation for RU
- Translations added for IT and FR
- Fixed lua bug when selling after unloading
- Created my own mod icon

Changelog 1.2.2.0
- Translations added for PL
- Predefines buttons for default gamepad

Changelog 1.3.0.0
- Changes to Mod Image and Description for the ModHub publish
- Added ES
- Loading and Unloading Areas can be shown now. Default [LCTRL] + [U]
- Loading is only shown in F1 when there is something to load, to not block Truck refill diesel
- Controls are only visible when the Trailer is active to solve problems with mutiple autloaders attached

Changelog 1.3.1.0
- Changes for ModHub publish

Changelog 1.4.0.0
- Add default round bales 125/150/180. Must be enabled by the modder of the trailer (useBales="true")

Changelog 1.4.1.0
- Size of liquid tank corrected for better loading
- Round bale loading optimized
- Icons for modder added in mod
- Translation in CZ
]]></en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Basis Mod für die Verwendung von Mods mit Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung.

Ein Vorbild wie die Spezialisierung einzubauen ist findest du im Strautmann SEK 802 Paletten Autoloader.
Aktuell sind nur Standard Europaletten, Flüssigkeitstanks, Bigbag Paletten und Rundballen möglich, weiteres wird folgen.

Bedienung:
Fahrt neben die Paletten um dann mit [R] das laden zu starten.
Achtet darauf, dass ihr auch die richtigen Palettenart ausgewählt habt.
Die Paletten liegen dann, wie von Hand geladen, auf der Ladefläche. 
Nicht vergessen das Ihr Spanngurte anlegt, sonst rutschen sie.
Ihr könnt die Entladeseite wählen und entladen.

Anleitungen zum Einbau und Hilfe findest du auf dem <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog 1.0.1.0:
- Fehler für Baumwollrundballen auf Dedi behoben
- kleine Anpassung am Lade/Entlade Verhalten um der Fehlerhaften Anzeige durch die Engine auf dem Dedi entgegenzuwirken

Changelog 1.2.0.0:
- Fehlende Übersetzungen für Shop eingefügt.
- Umstellung auf eigene Bindings, um Doppelbelegungen zu minimieren.
- Setzlingspaletten können jetzt mit Europlatten geladen werden.
- Neuer Ladetyp für überladene Europaletten wie z.B. die von KsAG oder Schaumann (geringere Ladekapazität).
- Ladeverhalten auf Automatisches Aufladen aller Paletten in Reichweite umgebaut. Einmal [R] drücken und alles wird aufgeladen.
- Palette von Pioneer fällt jetzt unter überladene Europaletten.

Changelog 1.2.1.0:
- RU Übersetzung verbessert
- Übersetzung in IT und FR
- lua Fehler beim verkaufen nach abladen behoben
- Eigenes Mod Icon erstellt.

Changelog 1.2.2.0:
- Übersetzung in PL
- Standard Gamepad Tasten vorbelegt

Changelog 1.3.0.0:
- Änderungen am Mod Icon und der Beschreibung für die ModHub-Veröffentlichung
- ES hinzugefügt
- Be- und Entladebereiche können jetzt angezeigt werden. Standard [LCTRL] + [U]
- Das Laden wird nur in F1 angezeigt, wenn es etwas zu laden gibt, um das tanken eines LKW nicht zu blockieren
- Steuerelemente sind nur sichtbar, wenn der Autoloader aktiv ist, um Probleme mit mehreren angeschlossenen Autoloadern zu beheben

Changelog 1.3.1.0:
- Änderungen für ModHub-Veröffentlichung

Changelog 1.4.0.0
- Standard-Rundballen 125/150/180 können jetzt geladen werden. Muss vom Modder des Trailers aktiviert werden (useBales="true")

Changelog 1.4.1.0
- Größe vom Flüssigkeitentank korrigiert für besseres Laden
- Rundballen Laden optimiert
- Icons für Modder in Mod eingefügt
- Übersetzung in CZ
]]>
        </de>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[Mod di base per l'utilizzo di mod con specializzazione caricamento automatico di pallet.

È possibile trovare un esempio di come deve essere incorporata la specializzazione nel caricamento automatico per pallet Strautmann SEK 802.
Attualmente sono possibili solo europallet standard, serbatoi per liquidi, pallet big bag e rotoballe, altri seguiranno.

Come si usa:
- Assicurati di aver selezionato il tipo di pallet corretto.
- Avvicinati ai pallet e poi col tasto [R] per caricare.
- I pallet sono quindi come caricati a mano sull'area di carico.
- Fissa il carico con le cinghie prima di guidare, altrimenti cascano a terra.
- Puoi scegliere il lato di scarico e scaricare col tasto I.

Changelog:
v1.0.1.0
- Risolto un bug per le balle rotonde di cotone su Dedi
- Piccolo aggiustamento al comportamento di carico/scarico per contrastare l'errata visualizzazione da parte del Engine sul Dedi

v1.2.0.0
- Aggiunte traduzioni mancanti per il negozio.
- Passaggio alle proprie associazioni per ridurre al minimo le doppie assegnazioni.
- Ora è possibile caricare i pallet di alberello con l'impostazione Europallet.
- Nuovo tipo di caricamento per Europallet sovradimensionati come quelli di KsAG o Schaumann (capacità di carico ridotta).
- Il comportamento di caricamento è stato convertito in caricamento automatico di tutti i tipi di pallet a portata del raggio d'azione. Basta premere una volta il tasto [R] e tutto viene caricato.
- Il pallet Pioneer è ora caricabile con l'impostazione sovradimensionata.

v1.2.1.0
- Traduzione migliorata per RU
- Aggiunta traduzione per IT e FR
- Corretto l'errore lua durante la vendita dopo lo scarico
- Creazione icona mod

v1.2.2.0
- Traduzione in PL
- Pulsanti predefiniti pre-assegnati per il gamepad

v1.3.0.0
- Modifiche all'icona Mod e alla descrizione per la pubblicazione sul ModHub
- Aggiunto ES
- Ora è possibile visualizzare le aree di carico e scarico. Tasti Predefiniti [LCTRL] + [U]
- Il caricamento viene mostrato in F1 solo quando c'è qualcosa da caricare in modo da non bloccare il rifornimento del veicolo
- I controlli sono visibili solo quando il trailer è attivo. Serve per risolvere i problemi con più caricatori automatici collegati

v1.3.1.0
- Modifiche per la pubblicazione di ModHub

v1.4.0.0
- Aggiungi rotoballe predefinite 125/150/180. Deve essere abilitato dal modder del trailer (useBales="true")

v1.4.1.0
- Dimensione del serbatoio dei liquidi corretta per un migliore caricamento
- Carico delle balle rotonde ottimizzato
- Icone per modder aggiunte al mod
- Traduzione in CZ
]]></it>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Mod de base pour l'utilisation de mods avec la spécialisation Pallet Autoload

Vous trouverez un exemple d'utilisation dans votre propre mod dans le Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Actuellement, seules les palettes européennes par défaut, les réservoirs de liquide, les palettes bigbag et les balles rondes sont possibles, d'autres suivront.

Comment utiliser:
Conduisez à côté des palettes, puis avec R, vous pouvez charger une palette après l'autre.
Assurez-vous d'avoir sélectionné le bon type de palette.
Les palettes sont alors comme chargées à la main sur la zone de chargement.
Fixez avec des sangles avant de conduire, sinon il tombe.
Vous pouvez choisir le côté de déchargement et le décharger.

Le istruzioni per l'integrazione e l'assistenza sono disponibili su <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Journal des modifications 1.0.1.0
- Erreur pour les balles carrées de coton sur Dedi résolue
- petite modification du comportement de chargement/déchargement pour lutter contre le mauvais affichage du moteur dans Dedi

Journal des modifications 1.2.0.0
- Traductions manquantes ajoutées pour la boutique.
- Modifiez les liaisons en liaisons configurables pour minimiser la double utilisation.
- Les palettes de gaules peuvent maintenant être chargées avec le réglage de l'Europalette.
- Nouveau type de chargement pour les europalettes surdimensionnées comme celles de KsAG ou Schaumann (capacité de chargement moindre).
- Modifiez le chargement pour charger automatiquement tout ce qui est à portée en appuyant une fois sur [R].
- La palette Pioneer est maintenant chargeable avec le réglage surdimensionné.

Journal des modifications 1.2.1.0
- Traduction améliorée pour RU
- Traductions ajoutées pour IT en FR
- Correction d'un bug lua lors de la vente après le déchargement
- Création de ma propre icône de mod

Journal des modifications 1.2.2.0
- Traduction en PL
- Boutons prédéfinis pour la manette de jeu par défaut

Journal des modifications 1.3.0.0
- Modifications de l'image et de la description du mod pour la publication ModHub
- ES ajoutée
- Les zones de chargement et de déchargement peuvent être affichées maintenant. Par défaut [LCTRL] + [U]
- Le chargement n'est affiché en F1 que lorsqu'il y a quelque chose à charger, pour ne pas bloquer la recharge diesel du camion
- Les commandes ne sont visibles que lorsque la remorque est active pour résoudre les problèmes avec plusieurs chargeurs automatiques attachés

Journal des modifications 1.3.1.0
- Modifications pour la publication ModHub

Journal des modifications 1.4.0.0
- Ajouter des balles rondes par défaut 125/150/180. Doit être activé par le moddeur de la bande-annonce (useBales="true")

Journal des modifications 1.4.1.0
- Correction de la taille du réservoir de liquide pour un meilleur chargement
- Optimisation du chargement des balles rondes
- Ajout d'icônes pour les moddeurs dans le mod
- Traduction en CZ
]]></fr>
        <es>
            <![CDATA[Mod base para usar Mods con la especialización Carga Automática Palés

Un ejemplo de cómo usarlo en su propio mod lo encontrará en Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Actualmente, solo admite los palés europeos (europalés) predeterminados, los tanques para líquidos (GRG), los palés de sacos grandes y las pacas redondas, seguirán más.

Cómo utilizar:
Conduzca junto a los palés y luego con [R] puede iniciar el proceso de carga.
Asegúrese de haber seleccionado el tipo de palé correcto.
Los palés se cargan entonces, como si se hubieran cargado a mano, en el área de carga.
Asegure la carga con las cintas tensoras antes de conducir, de lo contrario, se puede caer.
Puede elegir el lado de descarga y descargarlo.

Las instrucciones para la compilación y la ayuda que encontrará en <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Registro de cambios 1.0.1.0
- Error con las pacas redondas de algodón en Dedi solucionado
- Pequeño cambio en el comportamiento de carga/descarga para contrarrestar la visualización incorrecta de Engine en Dedi

Registro de cambios 1.2.0.0
- Se agregaron traducciones faltantes para la tienda.
- Cambiar los enlaces para que sean enlaces configurables para minimizar el doble uso.
- Los palés de plantones ahora se pueden cargar con la configuración de palé europeo.
- Nuevo tipo de carga para Europalés sobredimensionados como los de KsAG o Schaumann (menor capacidad de carga).
- Cambiado el comportamiento de carga para cargar automáticamente todo lo que está dentro del alcance con una sola pulsación de [R].
- El palé Pioneer ahora se puede cargar con la configuración de Europalés sobredimensionados.

Registro de cambios 1.2.1.0
- Traducción mejorada para RU
- Traducciones agregadas para IT en FR
- Se corrigió el error de lua al vender después de descargar
- Creé mi propio modIcon

Registro de cambios 1.2.2.0
- Traducción en PL
- Botones predefinidos para gamepad predeterminado

Registro de cambios 1.3.0.0
- Cambios en la imagen y la descripción de Mod para la publicación de ModHub
- ES añadida
- Ahora se pueden mostrar las áreas de carga y descarga. Predeterminado [LCTRL] + [U]
- La carga solo se muestra en F1 cuando hay algo que cargar, para no bloquear la recarga de diesel del camión.
- Los controles solo son visibles cuando el tráiler está activo para resolver problemas con múltiples cargadores automáticos conectados

Registro de cambios 1.3.1.0
- Cambios para la publicación de ModHub

Registro de cambios 1.4.0.0
- Agregar pacas redondas predeterminadas 125/150/180. Debe estar habilitado por el modder del tráiler (useBales="true")

Registro de cambios 1.4.1.0
- Tamaño del depósito de líquido corregido para una mejor carga
- Carga de pacas redondas optimizada
- Iconos para el modder añadidos al mod
- Traducción en CZ
]]>
        </es>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_LOAD_PALLET">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_r"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_11" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_10" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_u"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_13" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOAD">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_i"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_15" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_u"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="AL_LOAD_PALLET"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOAD"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS"/>
    </actions>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
</modDesc>