<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="65">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>1.7.3.0 RC2</version>
    <title>
        <en>Pallet Autoload Specialization</en>
        <de>Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung</de>
        <ru>Автопогрузка</ru>
        <it>Specializzazione Caricamento Automatico Pallet</it>
        <fr>Spécialisation De Chargement Automatique De Palettes</fr>
        <es>Especialización Carga Automática Palés</es>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Base Mod for using Mods with Pallet Autoload Specialization

An example of how to use in your own mod you will find in the Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Currently supported from the standard game:
- Standard Euro pallets
- Liquid tanks
- Big bag pallets
- Round bales
- Square bales 180/220/240
- Bigbags
Pallets from the following mods can be used:
- Package Of Premium Pallets And Bags
- HoT Fries Factory
In addition, all Euro pallets that are constructed according to the principle of the basic play pallets.

Operation:
Activate loading with [B] and then drive next to a pallet or bale to load it.
Make sure that you have selected the correct load.
The pallets or bales will then lie on the loading area as if they were loaded by hand. 
Do not forget to fasten the straps, otherwise they will slip.
You can select the unloading side with [U] and unload with [I].
The loading switches off automatically when there is no more loading area.
You can also switch it off yourself with [B].

Instructions for build in and help you will find on the <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog:
1.7.2.0
- The loading bay memory list is now also reset when the system is switched off.
- Autoloaders can no longer take pallets from the loading area of another autoloader (multiple trailers)
- onAIFieldWorker events implemented
- Tension belts now have a delay between loosening and tightening to improve server sync with patch 1.4. On the server 1.5 seconds in single player 0.2 seconds. Feedback on this is welcome.
- Dropped pallets or pallets taken down by hand are now not moved again during unloading

1.7.1.1
- Fix stream error
- Add missing translation

1.7.1.0
- Automatic tension belts on dedi server activated again regarding the settings the modder of the vehicle has defined.
- Automatic tension belts can now be activated/deactivated per vehicle by [lctrl]+[J]. This is stored per vehicle.
- Optimized searching valid load place by remembering invalid load places as long as the loader is active.
- add unloading side backwards for all vehicles by default. Position can configured by the modder.
- Changed priorities of the key binding to have important entries better visible in the F1 Help.

1.7.0.0
- Changed activation to LS standard for loading wagon [B] and always activatable. 
- Text of unloading page in F1 on Dedi fixed.
- Support of Multifruit Pack bales incl. lavender round bales (loadable as cotton round bales)
- Load only selectable when load mode is deactivated
- Automatic tightening straps on dedicated server disabled due to engine sync errors

1.6.2.0
- External access optimised
- Square bale loading behaviour optimised

1.6.1.2
- Fix for Wool pallet

1.6.1.0
- Possibility for external mods to access the functions created
- Selected cargo is now displayed as extra text in the help menu
- Palette sizes adapted to average values of new mods
- Automatic ratchet straps re-enabled on Dedi Server. Until Giants has patched this <a href="https://forbidden-mods.de/filebase/file/31066-tensionbelts-fix-for-1-3-patch/">this mod</a> is necessary.
- Modders can now also make their own palettes loadable through the folder structure. Details on the wiki.

1.6.0.0
- Modification of the communication with the Dedi Server to improve the performance.
- Loading mode now remains active until the trailer is full or it is switched off. Tension belts are tightened in between if the trailer supports it.
- Vehicle scheme shows when loading is activated.
- Maximum capacity displayed when load selection is made.
- Automatic tensioning straps deactivated on Dedi Server because of the bug from patch 1.3.

1.5.0.0
- Add default round bales 125/150/180. Must be enabled by the modder of the trailer (useBales="true")
- Size of liquid tank corrected for better loading
- Icons for modder added in mod
- Translation in CZ
- Bigbags added
- Translations improved
- Tension belts automatically tightened. Must be activated by the trailer modder (useTensionBelts="true")
- Bale loading in motion improved
- Support of mod "Package of Premium Pallets and Sacks".
- Support of mod "HoT Pommes Factory"
- Added square bales 180/220/240

1.3.1.0
- Changes to Mod Image and Description for the ModHub publish
- Added ES
- Loading and Unloading Areas can be shown now. Default [LCTRL] + [U]
- Loading is only shown in F1 when there is something to load, to not block Truck refill diesel
- Controls are only visible when the Trailer is active to solve problems with mutiple autloaders attached
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Basis Mod für die Verwendung von Mods mit Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung.

Ein Vorbild wie die Spezialisierung einzubauen ist findest du im Strautmann SEK 802 Paletten Autoloader.
Aktuell wird aus dem Standard Spiel unterstützt:
- Standard Europaletten
- Flüssigkeitstanks
- Bigbag Paletten
- Rundballen
- Quaderballen 180/220/240
- Bigbags
Paletten aus den folgenden Mods sind nutzbar:
- Paket Von Premium-Paletten Und Säcken
- HoT Pommes Factory
Außerdem alle Euro Paletten, die nach dem Prinzip der Basis Spiel Paletten aufgebaut sind.

Bedienung:
Aktiviert das Laden mit [B] und fahrt dann neben eine Palette oder einen Ballen um ihn auf zu laden.
Achtet darauf, dass ihr auch das richtige Ladegut ausgewählt habt.
Die Paletten oder Ballen liegen dann, wie von Hand geladen, auf der Ladefläche. 
Nicht vergessen das Ihr Spanngurte anlegt, sonst rutschen sie.
Ihr könnt die Entladeseite mit [U] wählen und mit [I] entladen.
Das Laden schaltet sich automatisch ab, wenn kein Ladeplatz mehr gefunden wird.
Ihr könnt es aber auch mit [B] wieder selbst abschalten.

Anleitungen zum Einbau und Hilfe findest du auf dem <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog:
1.7.3.0
- Fix für Triggerfehler aus Patch 1.4

1.7.2.0
- Merkliste der Ladeplätze wird beim abschalten jetzt auch zurückgesetzt
- Autoloader können sich die Paletten nicht mehr von der Ladefläche eines anderen Autoloaders weg nehmen (mehrfache Anhänger)
- onAIFieldWorker events implementiert
- Spanngurte haben nun eine Verzögerung zwischen lösen und anziehen zu Verbesserung der Server sync mit Patch 1.4. Auf dem Server 1,5 Sekunden im Single Player 0,2 Sekunden. Rückmeldungen hierzu sind erwünscht.
- Runtergefallene oder von Hand runtergenommene Paletten werden jetzt beim abladen nicht noch mal versetzt

1.7.1.1
- Stream-Fehler behoben
- Fehlende Übersetzung hinzufügen

1.7.1.0
- Automatische Spanngurte auf dem dedi-Server sind wieder aktiviert und berücksichtigen die Einstellungen, die der Modder des Fahrzeugs festgelegt hat.
- Automatische Spanngurte können nun pro Fahrzeug mit [lctrl]+[J] aktiviert/deaktiviert werden. Dies wird pro Fahrzeug gespeichert.
- Die Suche nach gültigen Ladeplätzen wurde optimiert, indem ungültige Ladeplätze gespeichert werden, solange der Lader aktiv ist.
- Entladeseite rückwärts für alle Fahrzeuge als Standard hinzufügen. Position kann vom Modder konfiguriert werden.
- Prioritäten der Tastenbelegung geändert, um wichtige Einträge in der F1-Hilfe besser sichtbar zu machen.

1.7.0.0
- Änderung der Aktivierung auf LS Standard für Ladewagen [B] und immer aktivierbar. 
- Text der Entladeseite im F1 auf Dedi gefixed
- Support von Multifruit Pack Ballen inkl. Lavendel Rundballen (ladebar als Baumwoll Rundballen)
- Ladegut nur noch wählbar, wenn der Lademodus deaktiviert ist
- Automatische Spanngurte auf Dedicated Server deaktiviert wegen der Sync Fehler der Engine

1.6.2.0
- Externe Zugriffsmöglichkeiten optimiert
- Quaderballen Ladeverhalten optimiert

1.6.1.2
- Fix für Wollpalette

1.6.1.0
- Möglichkeit für externe Mods zum zugriff auf die Funktionen geschaffen
- Gewähltes Ladegut wird jetzt als Extra Text im Hilfe Menü angezeigt
- Paletten Größen angepasst an durchnittliche Werte neuer Mods
- Automatische Spanngurte wieder aktiviert auf Dedi Server. Bis Giants das gepatched hat ist <a href="https://forbidden-mods.de/filebase/file/31066-tensionbelts-fix-for-1-3-patch/">dieser Mod</a> notwendig.
- Modder können ihre eigenen Paletten nun zusätzlich durch die Ordnerstruktur ladbar machen. Details im Wiki.

1.6.0.0
- Umbau der Kommunikation mit dem Dedi Server zur Verbesserung der Performance.
- Lademodus bleibt nun aktiv bis der Trailer voll ist oder er abgeschaltet wird. Spangurte werden zwischendurch angezogen, wenn der Trailer das unterstützt.
- Fahrzeug Schema zeigt an, wenn das Laden aktiviert ist.
- Anzeige der Maximal Kapazität bei der Ladegutauswahl.
- Automatische Spanngurte deaktiviert auf Dedi Server wegen dem Fehler aus Patch 1.3

1.5.0.0
- Standard-Rundballen 125/150/180 können jetzt geladen werden. Muss vom Modder des Trailers aktiviert werden (useBales="true")
- Größe vom Flüssigkeitentank korrigiert für besseres Laden
- Icons für Modder in Mod eingefügt
- Übersetzung in CZ
- Bigbags hinzugefügt
- Übersetzungen verbessert
- Spanngurte automatisch anziehen. Muss vom Modder des Trailers aktiviert werden (useTensionBelts="true")
- Support von Mod "Paket Von Premium-Paletten Und Säcken"
- Support von Mod "HoT Pommes Factory"
- Quaderballen 180/220/240 hinzugefügt

1.3.1.0
- Änderungen am Mod Icon und der Beschreibung für die ModHub-Veröffentlichung
- ES hinzugefügt
- Be- und Entladebereiche können jetzt angezeigt werden. Standard [LCTRL] + [U]
- Das Laden wird nur in F1 angezeigt, wenn es etwas zu laden gibt, um das tanken eines LKW nicht zu blockieren
- Steuerelemente sind nur sichtbar, wenn der Autoloader aktiv ist, um Probleme mit mehreren angeschlossenen Autoloadern zu beheben
]]>
        </de>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[Mod di base per l'utilizzo di mod con specializzazione caricamento automatico di pallet.

È possibile trovare un esempio di come deve essere incorporata la specializzazione nel caricamento automatico per pallet Strautmann SEK 802.
Attualmente supportato dal gioco standard:
- Euro pallet standard
- Serbatoi per liquidi
- Pallet di borse grandi
- Balle rotonde
- Balle quadrate 180/220/240
- Bigbags
Si possono usare i pallet dei seguenti mod:
- Pacchetto di pallet e borse Premium
- Fabbrica di patatine fritte HoT
Inoltre, tutti gli Euro pallet che sono costruiti secondo il principio dei pallet di base del gioco.

Operazione:
Attivare il caricamento con [B] e poi guidare accanto a un pallet o a una balla per caricarla.
Assicuratevi di aver selezionato il carico corretto.
I pallet o le balle giacciono poi sull'area di carico come se fossero stati caricati a mano. 
Non dimenticate di allacciare le cinghie, altrimenti scivoleranno.
Potete selezionare il lato di scarico con [U] e scaricare con [I].
Il caricamento si spegne automaticamente quando non c'è più area di carico.
Potete anche spegnerlo voi stessi con [B].

Changelog:
1.7.2.0
- La lista della memoria della baia di carico viene ora resettata anche quando il sistema viene spento.
- Gli autoloader non possono più prendere pallet dall'area di carico di un altro autoloader (rimorchi multipli)
- eventi onAIFieldWorker implementati
- Le cinghie di tensione ora hanno un ritardo tra l'allentamento e il serraggio per migliorare la sincronizzazione del server con la patch 1.4. Sul server 1,5 secondi in single player 0,2 secondi. Il feedback su questo è benvenuto.
- I pallet caduti o i pallet presi a mano non vengono più spostati durante lo scarico

1.7.1.1
- Fissa l'errore di flusso
- Aggiungere la traduzione mancante

1.7.1.0
- Le cinghie di tensione automatiche sul server dedi si attivano di nuovo regolando le impostazioni che il modder del veicolo ha definito.
- Le cinghie di tensione automatiche possono ora essere attivate/disattivate per veicolo con [lctrl]+[J]. Questo viene memorizzato per veicolo.
- Ottimizzare la ricerca di posti di carico validi ricordando i posti di carico non validi finché il caricatore è attivo.
- aggiungere il lato di scarico all'indietro per tutti i veicoli in modo predefinito. La posizione può essere configurata dal modder.
- Cambiare le priorità del keybinding per avere controlli principali meglio visibili nella Guida F1.

1.7.0.0
- Cambiata l'attivazione a LS standard per il carro di carico [B] e sempre attivabile. 
- Testo di scarico della pagina in F1 su Dedi corretto.
- Supporto di balle Multifruit Pack incl. balle rotonde di lavanda (caricabili come balle rotonde di cotone)
- Carico selezionabile solo quando la modalità di carico è disattivata
- Cinghie di serraggio automatiche sul server dedicato disattivate a causa di errori di sincronizzazione del motore

1.6.2.0
- Accesso esterno ottimizzato
- Comportamento di carico delle balle quadrate ottimizzato

1.6.1.2
- Fix for Wool pallet

1.6.1.0
- Possibilità per mod esterne di accedere alle funzioni create
- Il carico selezionato viene ora visualizzato come testo extra nel menu di aiuto
- Dimensioni della tavolozza adattate ai valori medi delle nuove mod
- Cinghie a cricchetto automatiche riabilitate su Dedi Server. Fino a quando Giants non avrà corretto questa <a href="https://forbidden-mods.de/filebase/file/31066-tensionbelts-fix-for-1-3-patch/">questa mod</a> è necessaria.
- I modder ora possono anche rendere caricabili le proprie tavolozze attraverso la struttura delle cartelle. Dettagli sul wiki.

1.6.0.0
- Modifica della comunicazione con il server Dedi per migliorare le prestazioni.
- La modalità di carico ora rimane attiva fino a quando il rimorchio è pieno o viene spento. Le cinghie di tensione si stringono tra loro se il rimorchio lo sostiene.
- Lo schema del veicolo mostra quando il caricamento è attivato.
- Capacità massima visualizzata quando si seleziona il carico.
- Cinghie di tensionamento automatico disattivate su Dedi Server a causa del bug della patch 1.3.

1.5.0.0
- Aggiungi rotoballe predefinite 125/150/180. Deve essere abilitato dal modder del trailer (useBales="true")
- Dimensione del serbatoio dei liquidi corretta per un migliore caricamento
- Icone per modder aggiunte al mod
- Traduzione in CZ
- Bigbags ha aggiunto
- Traduzioni migliorate
- Le cinghie di tensione si stringono automaticamente. Deve essere attivato dal modder del rimorchio (useTensionBelts="true")
- Supporto del mod "Pacchetto di pallet e sacchi Premium".
- Supporto del mod "HoT Pommes Factory
- Aggiunta di balle quadrate 180/220/240

1.3.1.0
- Modifiche all'icona Mod e alla descrizione per la pubblicazione sul ModHub
- Aggiunto ES
- Ora è possibile visualizzare le aree di carico e scarico. Tasti Predefiniti [LCTRL] + [U]
- Il caricamento viene mostrato in F1 solo quando c'è qualcosa da caricare in modo da non bloccare il rifornimento del veicolo
- I controlli sono visibili solo quando il trailer è attivo. Serve per risolvere i problemi con più caricatori automatici collegati
]]>
        </it>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Mod de base pour l'utilisation de mods avec la spécialisation Pallet Autoload

Vous trouverez un exemple d'utilisation dans votre propre mod dans le Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Actuellement, le jeu standard est pris en charge :
- Europalettes standard
- Réservoirs de liquide
- Palettes bigbag
- Balles rondes
- Balles cubiques 180/220/240
- Bigbags
Les palettes des Mods suivants sont utilisables :
- Paquet De Palettes Premium Et De Sacs
- Usine de frites HoT
En outre, toutes les palettes Europe construites selon le principe des palettes de jeu de base.

Manipulation :
Active le chargement avec [B] et roule ensuite à côté d'une palette ou d'une balle pour la charger.
Veillez à ce que vous ayez sélectionné le bon chargement.
Les palettes ou les balles sont alors posées sur la surface de chargement comme si elles étaient chargées manuellement. 
N'oubliez pas d'attacher les sangles, sinon elles glisseront.
Vous pouvez sélectionner le côté de déchargement avec [U] et décharger avec [I].
Le chargement s'arrête automatiquement lorsqu'il n'y a plus de surface de chargement.
Vous pouvez également le désactiver vous-même avec [B].

Le istruzioni per l'integrazione e l'assistenza sono disponibili su <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Journal des modifications:
1.7.2.0
- La liste de mémorisation des emplacements de chargement est désormais réinitialisée lors de la désactivation.
- Les autochargeurs ne peuvent plus prendre les palettes de l'aire de chargement d'un autre autochargeur (remorques multiples).
- Implémentation des événements onAIFieldWorker.
- Les sangles de serrage ont désormais un délai entre le desserrage et le serrage pour améliorer la synchronisation du serveur avec le patch 1.4. 1,5 seconde sur le serveur et 0,2 seconde en mode solo. Les commentaires à ce sujet sont les bienvenus.
- Les palettes tombées ou enlevées manuellement ne sont plus déplacées lors du déchargement.

1.7.1.1
- Correction d'une erreur de flux
- Ajout de la traduction manquante

1.7.1.0
- Les courroies de tension automatiques sur le serveur dedi sont à nouveau activées en fonction des paramètres définis par le moddeur du véhicule.
- Les courroies de tension automatiques peuvent maintenant être activées/désactivées par véhicule par [lctrl]+[J]. Ceci est stocké par véhicule.
- Optimisation de la recherche de lieux de chargement valides en mémorisant les lieux de chargement invalides tant que le chargeur est actif.
- Ajout d'un côté de déchargement en arrière pour tous les véhicules par défaut. La position peut être configurée par le moddeur.
- Changement des priorités du keybinding pour que les contrôles principaux soient mieux visibles dans l'aide F1.

1.7.0.0
- Changement de l'activation en LS standard pour les autochargeuses [B] et toujours activable. 
- Correction du texte de la page de déchargement dans le F1 sur Dedi.
- Support des balles Multifruit Pack, y compris les balles rondes de lavande (chargeables comme des balles rondes de coton).
- Le chargement ne peut plus être sélectionné que si le mode de chargement est désactivé
- Sangles de serrage automatique désactivées sur les serveurs dédiés en raison des erreurs de synchronisation du moteur

1.6.2.0
- Accès externe optimisé
- Comportement de chargement des balles cubiques optimisé

1.6.1.2
- Fix for Wool pallet

1.6.1.0
- Possibilité pour les mods externes d'accéder aux fonctions créées
- La cargaison sélectionnée est maintenant affichée sous forme de texte supplémentaire dans le menu d'aide
- Tailles de palettes adaptées aux valeurs moyennes des nouveaux mods
- Sangles à cliquet automatiques réactivées sur Dedi Server. Jusqu'à ce que Giants ait corrigé ce <a href="https://forbidden-mods.de/filebase/file/31066-tensionbelts-fix-for-1-3-patch/">ce mod</a> est nécessaire.
- Les moddeurs peuvent désormais rendre leurs propres palettes chargeables via la structure des dossiers. Détails sur le wiki.

1.6.0.0
- Modification de la communication avec le serveur Dedi pour améliorer les performances.
- Le mode de chargement reste désormais actif jusqu'à ce que la remorque soit pleine ou qu'elle soit éteinte. Les ceintures de sécurité sont mises en place de temps en temps si la remorque le permet.
- Le schéma du véhicule indique si le chargement est activé.
- Affichage de la capacité maximale lors de la sélection du chargement.
- Sangles automatiques désactivées sur le serveur Dedi à cause du bug du patch 1.3.

1.5.0.0
- Ajouter des balles rondes par défaut 125/150/180. Doit être activé par le moddeur de la bande-annonce (useBales="true")
- Correction de la taille du réservoir de liquide pour un meilleur chargement
- Ajout d'icônes pour les moddeurs dans le mod
- Traduction en CZ
- Ajout de bigbags
- amélioration des traductions
- Serrage automatique des sangles de serrage. Doit être activé par le moddeur de la remorque (useTensionBelts="true").
- Support du mod "Paquet de palettes Premium et de sacs".
- Support du mod "HoT Pommes Factory".
- Ajout des balles cubiques 180/220/240

1.3.1.0
- Modifications de l'image et de la description du mod pour la publication ModHub
- ES ajoutée
- Les zones de chargement et de déchargement peuvent être affichées maintenant. Par défaut [LCTRL] + [U]
- Le chargement n'est affiché en F1 que lorsqu'il y a quelque chose à charger, pour ne pas bloquer la recharge diesel du camion
- Les commandes ne sont visibles que lorsque la remorque est active pour résoudre les problèmes avec plusieurs chargeurs automatiques attachés
]]>
        </fr>
        <es>
            <![CDATA[Mod base para usar Mods con la especialización Carga Automática Palés

Un ejemplo de cómo usarlo en su propio mod lo encontrará en Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Actualmente es compatible con el juego estándar:
- Europalets estándar
- Tanques de líquido
- Paletas Big bag
- Pacas redondas
- Pacas cuadradas 180/220/240
- Bigbags
Se pueden utilizar las paletas de los siguientes mods:
- Paquete de paletas y bolsas de primera calidad
- Fábrica de patatas fritas HoT
Además, todas las europaletas que se construyen según el principio de las paletas de juego básicas.

Operación:
Active la carga con [B] y luego conduzca junto a un palé o paca para cargarlo.
Asegúrese de que ha seleccionado la carga correcta.
Las paletas o balas se depositarán entonces en la zona de carga como si se hubieran cargado a mano. 
No olvides abrochar las correas, de lo contrario se deslizarán.
Puede seleccionar el lado de descarga con [U] y descargar con [I].
La carga se desconecta automáticamente cuando no hay más zona de carga.
También puedes apagarlo tú mismo con [B].

Las instrucciones para la compilación y la ayuda que encontrará en <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Registro de cambios:
1.7.2.0
- La lista de la memoria del muelle de carga ahora también se restablece cuando se apaga el sistema.
- Los autocargadores ya no pueden tomar palés de la zona de carga de otro autocargador (remolques múltiples)
- Eventos onAIFieldWorker implementados
- Los cinturones de tensión tienen ahora un retardo entre el aflojamiento y el apriete para mejorar la sincronización con el servidor con el parche 1.4. En el servidor 1,5 segundos en el jugador individual 0,2 segundos. Se agradecen los comentarios al respecto.
- Las paletas que se caen o que se bajan a mano no se vuelven a mover durante la descarga

1.7.1.1
- Corregir el error de flujo
- Añadir la traducción que falta

1.7.1.0
- Los cinturones de tensión automáticos en el servidor dedi vuelven a activarse reguardando los ajustes que el modder del vehículo ha definido.
- Los cinturones de tensión automáticos pueden ahora ser activados/desactivados por vehículo mediante [lctrl]+[J]. Esto se almacena por vehículo.
- Optimizar la búsqueda de lugares de carga válidos recordando los lugares de carga no válidos mientras el cargador esté activo.
- Añadir el lado de descarga hacia atrás para todos los vehículos por defecto. La posición puede ser configurada por el modder.
- Cambiar las prioridades del keybinding para que los controles principales sean más visibles en la Ayuda F1.

1.7.0.0
- Se ha cambiado la activación a la norma LS para el vagón de carga [B] y siempre se puede activar. 
- Texto de descarga de la página en F1 en Dedi arreglado.
- Soporte de balas Multifruit Pack incl. balas redondas de lavanda (cargables como balas redondas de algodón)
- Carga sólo seleccionable cuando el modo de carga está desactivado
- Desactivación de las correas de apriete automático en el servidor dedicado debido a errores de sincronización del motor

1.6.2.0
- Acceso externo optimizado
- Comportamiento de carga de balas cuadradas optimizado

1.6.1.2
- Fix for Wool pallet

1.6.1.0
- Posibilidad de mods externos para acceder a las funciones creadas
- La carga seleccionada ahora se muestra como texto adicional en el menú de ayuda
- Tamaños de paleta adaptados a valores medios de nuevos mods.
- Correas de trinquete automáticas reactivadas en Dedi Server. Hasta que Giants haya parcheado este <a href="https://forbidden-mods.de/filebase/file/31066-tensionbelts-fix-for-1-3-patch/">este mod</a> es necesario.
- Los modders ahora también pueden hacer que sus propias paletas se puedan cargar a través de la estructura de carpetas. Detalles en la wiki.

1.6.0.0
- Modificación de la comunicación con el Servidor Dedi para mejorar el rendimiento.
- El modo de carga ahora permanece activo hasta que el remolque esté lleno o se apague. Los cinturones de tensión se tensan entre ellos si el remolque lo soporta.
- El esquema del vehículo muestra cuando se activa la carga.
- Visualización de la capacidad máxima durante la selección de la carga.
- Correas de tensión automáticas desactivadas en el Servidor Dedi debido al error del parche 1.3.

1.5.0.0
- Agregar pacas redondas predeterminadas 125/150/180. Debe estar habilitado por el modder del tráiler (useBales="true")
- Tamaño del depósito de líquido corregido para una mejor carga
- Iconos para el modder añadidos al mod
- Traducción en CZ
- Bigbags añadió
- Mejora de las traducciones
- Las correas de tensión se tensan automáticamente. Debe ser activado por el modder del remolque (useTensionBelts="true")
- Soporte del mod "Paquete de Paletas y Sacos Premium".
- Soporte del mod "HoT Pommes Factory
- Pacas cuadradas añadidas 180/220/240

1.3.1.0
- Cambios en la imagen y la descripción de Mod para la publicación de ModHub
- ES añadida
- Ahora se pueden mostrar las áreas de carga y descarga. Predeterminado [LCTRL] + [U]
- La carga solo se muestra en F1 cuando hay algo que cargar, para no bloquear la recarga de diesel del camión.
- Los controles solo son visibles cuando el tráiler está activo para resolver problemas con múltiples cargadores automáticos conectados
]]>
        </es>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_LOAD_PALLET">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_b"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_4" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_10" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_u"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_13" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOAD">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_i"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_15" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_u"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_AUTOMATIC_TENSIONBELTS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_j"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="AL_LOAD_PALLET"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOAD"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_AUTOMATIC_TENSIONBELTS"/>
    </actions>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
</modDesc>