<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="67">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>1.8.5.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>Pallet Autoload Specialization</en>
        <de>Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung</de>
        <ru>Автопогрузка</ru>
        <it>Specializzazione Caricamento Automatico Pallet</it>
        <fr>Spécialisation De Chargement Automatique De Palettes</fr>
        <es>Especialización Carga Automática Palés</es>
        <br>Especialização Em Carregamento Automático De Paletes</br>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Base Mod for using Mods with Pallet Autoload Specialization

An example of how to use in your own mod you will find in the Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Currently supported from the standard game:
- Standard Euro pallets
- Liquid tanks
- Big bag pallets
- Round bales
- Square bales 120/180/220/240
- Bigbags
Pallets from the following mods can be used:
- Package Of Premium Pallets And Bags
- HoT Fries Factory
In addition, all Euro pallets that are constructed according to the principle of the basic play pallets.

Operation:
Activate loading with [B] and then drive next to a pallet or bale to load it.
Make sure that you have selected the correct load.
The pallets or bales will then lie on the loading area as if they were loaded by hand. 
Do not forget to fasten the straps, otherwise they will slip.
You can select the unloading side with [U] and unload with [I].
The loading switches off automatically when there is no more loading area.
You can also switch it off yourself with [B].

Instructions for build in and help you will find on the <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog:
1.8.5.1
- Extension of the selectable load can now be done with mods via script.
- Mod icon improved
- Pallets are now also recognised if they are not directly of the type "pallet"

1.8.4.1
- Add usePalletWeightReduction config setting to reduce pallet weight on loading. Default is true
- Cleaned up changelog

1.8.3.1
- better possibilities of loading state for CP
- BR translation added

1.8.2.0
- new functions for reading the bale status added
- Bales are no longer pulled out of the bale chamber or wrapper.

1.8.1.0
- SV translations added
- Cotton bales simplified in recognition
- Correction for square bales with small loading areas
- Eventlistener deregistered for non AL configuration to improve performance
- Move unloading area in F1 menu only show if markers are visible.

1.8.0.1
- fix unloading position on dedicated server
- RU translation fixed by Nagor

1.8.0.0
- Code optimizations and use of Giants Timer because of crashes
- unloading area can be moved (will be reset when unloading)
- Markers are automatically shown when moving and selecting a page and only then can the page be changed.
- Markers are automatically hidden when unloading
- Blocking of vehicle unloading triggers on the loading area to reduce side effects caused by the faults in base game trigger
- New loading pattern, if more can fit on the surface by loading one lengthwise and the rest crosswise
- 120 square bales added. Be careful, they are not very stable due to their size.
- Connection with CP optimised
- maxObjects and height can now be defined per load by the modder, if they deviate from the default

1.7.3.0
- Lua Trigger error solved caused by update 1.4
- Tension Belt trigger reworked
- Autoloaders can no longer take pallets from the loading area of another autoloader (multiple trailers)
- onAIFieldWorker events implemented
- Tension belts now have a delay between loosening and tightening to improve server sync. On the server 1.5 seconds in single player 0.2 seconds. Feedback on this is welcome.
- Dropped pallets or pallets taken down by hand are now not moved again during unloading
- Automatic tension belts can now be activated/deactivated per vehicle by [lctrl]+[J]. This is stored per vehicle.
- Optimized searching valid load place by remembering invalid load places as long as the loader is active.
- add unloading side backwards for all vehicles by default. Position can configured by the modder.
- Changed priorities of the key binding to have important entries better visible in the F1 Help.
- Changed activation to LS standard for loading wagon [B] and always activatable. 
- Text of unloading page in F1 on Dedi fixed.
- Support of Multifruit Pack bales incl. lavender round bales (loadable as cotton round bales)
- Load only selectable when load mode is deactivated

1.6.2.0
- Square bale loading behaviour optimised
- Fix for Wool pallet
- Possibility for external mods to access the functions created
- Selected cargo is now displayed as extra text in the help menu
- Palette sizes adapted to average values of new mods
- Modders can now also make their own palettes loadable through the folder structure. Details on the wiki.
- Modification of the communication with the Dedi Server to improve the performance.
- Loading mode now remains active until the trailer is full or it is switched off. Tension belts are tightened in between if the trailer supports it.
- Vehicle scheme shows when loading is activated.
- Maximum capacity displayed when load selection is made.

1.5.0.0
- Add default round bales 125/150/180. Must be enabled by the modder of the trailer (useBales="true")
- Size of liquid tank corrected for better loading
- Icons for modder added in mod
- Translation in CZ
- Bigbags added
- Translations improved
- Tension belts automatically tightened. Must be activated by the trailer modder (useTensionBelts="true")
- Bale loading in motion improved
- Support of mod "Package of Premium Pallets and Sacks".
- Support of mod "HoT Pommes Factory"
- Added square bales 180/220/240
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Basis Mod für die Verwendung von Mods mit Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung.

Ein Vorbild wie die Spezialisierung einzubauen ist findest du im Strautmann SEK 802 Paletten Autoloader.
Aktuell wird aus dem Standard Spiel unterstützt:
- Standard Europaletten
- Flüssigkeitstanks
- Bigbag Paletten
- Rundballen
- Quaderballen 120/180/220/240
- Bigbags
Paletten aus den folgenden Mods sind nutzbar:
- Paket Von Premium-Paletten Und Säcken
- HoT Pommes Factory
Außerdem alle Euro Paletten, die nach dem Prinzip der Basis Spiel Paletten aufgebaut sind.

Bedienung:
Aktiviert das Laden mit [B] und fahrt dann neben eine Palette oder einen Ballen um ihn auf zu laden.
Achtet darauf, dass ihr auch das richtige Ladegut ausgewählt habt.
Die Paletten oder Ballen liegen dann, wie von Hand geladen, auf der Ladefläche. 
Nicht vergessen das Ihr Spanngurte anlegt, sonst rutschen sie.
Ihr könnt die Entladeseite mit [U] wählen und mit [I] entladen.
Das Laden schaltet sich automatisch ab, wenn kein Ladeplatz mehr gefunden wird.
Ihr könnt es aber auch mit [B] wieder selbst abschalten.

Anleitungen zum Einbau und Hilfe findest du auf dem <a href="https://bitbucket.org/Achimobil79/ls22_palletautoloader/wiki/Home">Bitbucket Wiki</a>

Changelog:
1.8.5.1
- Erweiterung des auswählbaren Ladeguts kann jetzt mit mods per skript gemacht werden.
- Mod Icon verbessert
- Paletten werden jetzt auch erkannt, wenn diese nicht direkt vom typ "pallet" sind.

1.8.4.1
- usePalletWeightReduction Konfiguration eingefügt zur Reduzierung des Gewichts von geladenen Paletten. Default true
- Changelog aufgeräumt

1.8.3.1
- Bessere Möglichkeit für CP zum erkennen vom Ballenladestatus
- BR Übersetzung hinzugefügt

1.8.2.0
- neue Funktionen zum auslesen des Ballen status eingefügt
- Ballen werden jetzt nicht mehr aus der Presskammer oder dem Wickler gezogen

1.8.1.0
- SV Übersetzungen hinzugefügt
- Baumwollballen vereinfacht in der Erkennung
- Korrektur für Quaderballen bei kleinen Ladeflächen
- Eventlistener bei nicht AL Konfiguration deregistriert zur verbesserung der Performance
- Verschieben der Abladefläche im F1 Menü nur anzeigen, wenn Markierungen sichtbar sind.

1.8.0.1
- Abladeposition auf dedicated Server gefixed
- RU Übersetzungen von Nagor verbessert

1.8.0.0
- Code Optimierungen und Verwendung von Giants Timer wegen abstürzen
- Abladebereich verschiebbar (wird beim abladen wieder zurückgesetzt)
- Markierungen werden beim Verschieben und Seite wählen automatisch eingeblendet und erst dann kann die Seite geändert werden
- Markierungen werden beim Abladen automatisch ausgeblendet
- Blockieren von Fahrzeugentladetriggern auf der Ladefläche zur Verringerung von Seiteneffekten durch die defekten Giants trigger
- Neues Lademuster, wenn mehr auf die Fläche passt durch eine längs und den Rest quer zu laden
- 120er Quaderballen eingefügt. Vorsicht, die sind aufgrund ihrer Größe nicht sehr stabil
- Verbindung mit CP überarbeitet
- maxObjects und height können jetzt pro Ladegut vom Modder definiert werden, wenn diese vom default abweichen

1.7.3.0
- Lua-Trigger-Fehler behoben, der durch Update 1.4 verursacht wurde
- Tension Belt Trigger überarbeitet
- Autoloader können sich die Paletten nicht mehr von der Ladefläche eines anderen Autoloaders weg nehmen (mehrfache Anhänger)
- onAIFieldWorker events implementiert
- Spanngurte haben nun eine Verzögerung zwischen lösen und anziehen zu Verbesserung der Server sync. Auf dem Server 1,5 Sekunden im Single Player 0,2 Sekunden. Rückmeldungen hierzu sind erwünscht.
- Runtergefallene oder von Hand runtergenommene Paletten werden jetzt beim abladen nicht noch mal versetzt
- Automatische Spanngurte können nun pro Fahrzeug mit [lctrl]+[J] aktiviert/deaktiviert werden. Dies wird pro Fahrzeug gespeichert.
- Die Suche nach gültigen Ladeplätzen wurde optimiert, indem ungültige Ladeplätze gespeichert werden, solange der Lader aktiv ist.
- Entladeseite rückwärts für alle Fahrzeuge als Standard hinzufügen. Position kann vom Modder konfiguriert werden.
- Prioritäten der Tastenbelegung geändert, um wichtige Einträge in der F1-Hilfe besser sichtbar zu machen.
- Änderung der Aktivierung auf LS Standard für Ladewagen [B] und immer aktivierbar. 
- Text der Entladeseite im F1 auf Dedi gefixed
- Support von Multifruit Pack Ballen inkl. Lavendel Rundballen (ladebar als Baumwoll Rundballen)
- Ladegut nur noch wählbar, wenn der Lademodus deaktiviert ist

1.6.2.0
- Quaderballen Ladeverhalten optimiert
- Fix für Wollpalette
- Möglichkeit für externe Mods zum zugriff auf die Funktionen geschaffen
- Gewähltes Ladegut wird jetzt als Extra Text im Hilfe Menü angezeigt
- Paletten Größen angepasst an durchnittliche Werte neuer Mods
- Modder können ihre eigenen Paletten nun zusätzlich durch die Ordnerstruktur ladbar machen. Details im Wiki.
- Umbau der Kommunikation mit dem Dedi Server zur Verbesserung der Performance.
- Lademodus bleibt nun aktiv bis der Trailer voll ist oder er abgeschaltet wird. Spangurte werden zwischendurch angezogen, wenn der Trailer das unterstützt.
- Fahrzeug Schema zeigt an, wenn das Laden aktiviert ist.
- Anzeige der Maximal Kapazität bei der Ladegutauswahl.

1.5.0.0
- Standard-Rundballen 125/150/180 können jetzt geladen werden. Muss vom Modder des Trailers aktiviert werden (useBales="true")
- Größe vom Flüssigkeitentank korrigiert für besseres Laden
- Icons für Modder in Mod eingefügt
- Übersetzung in CZ
- Bigbags hinzugefügt
- Übersetzungen verbessert
- Spanngurte automatisch anziehen. Muss vom Modder des Trailers aktiviert werden (useTensionBelts="true")
- Support von Mod "Paket Von Premium-Paletten Und Säcken"
- Support von Mod "HoT Pommes Factory"
- Quaderballen 180/220/240 hinzugefügt
]]>
        </de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_LOAD_PALLET">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_b"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_4" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_10" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_u"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_13" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOAD">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_i"/>
            <binding device="0_XINPUT_GAMEPAD" input="BUTTON_15" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_u"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_AUTOMATIC_TENSIONBELTS">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_j"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_UPDOWN">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_e" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_q" axisComponent="-" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_LEFTRIGHT">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_a" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_d" axisComponent="-" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_FRONTBACK">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_w" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_s" axisComponent="-" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="AL_LOAD_PALLET"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOAD"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_MARKERS"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_AUTOMATIC_TENSIONBELTS"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_UPDOWN" axisType="FULL"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_LEFTRIGHT" axisType="FULL"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOADAREA_MOVE_FRONTBACK" axisType="FULL"/>
    </actions>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
</modDesc>