<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>Achimobil</author>
    <version>1.2.1.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Pallet Autoload Specialization</en>
        <de>Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung</de>
        <ru>Автопогрузка</ru>
        <it>Specializzazione caricamento automatico pallet</it>
        <fr>Spécialisation de chargement automatique de palettes</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[Base Mod for using Mods with Pallet Autoload Specialization

An example of how to use in your own mod you will find in the Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Currently only default Euro pallets, liquidTanks, bigbag pallets and Cotton Square Bales are possible, more will follow.

How to use:
Drive next to the pallets and then with [R] you can start the loading process.
Make sure you have selected the correct pallet type.
The pallets are then as loaded by hand on the loading area. 
Fasten with straps before you drive, otherwise it fell of.
You can choose the unloading side and unload it.

Changelog 1.0.1.0
- Error for Cotton Square Bales on Dedi solved
- small changed loading/unloading behavior to work against the wrong display of the Giants Engine in Dedi

Changelog 1.2.0.0
- Missing translations added for shop.
- Change bindings to be configurable bindings for minimizing double usage.
- Sapling pallets could now be loaded with the Euro pallet setting. 
- New loading type for oversized Europallets like the ones from KsAG or Schaumann (smaller loading capacity).
- Change loading to load everything automatic what is in range with one time pressing [R].
- Pioneer pallet is now loadable with the oversized setting.

Changelog 1.2.1.0
- Improved translation for RU by Nagor
- Translation added for IT by Markus33 [ITA]
- Translations added for FR stolen from Illegal new release of my mod by BOB51160
- Fixed lua bug when selling after unloading
- Created my own mod icon
]]></en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Basis Mod für die Verwendung von Mods mit Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung.

Ein Vorbild wie die Spezialisierung einzubauen ist findest du im Strautmann SEK 802 Paletten Autoloader.
Aktuell sind nur Standard Europaletten, Flüssigkeitentanks, Bigbag Paletten und Baumwollrundballen möglich, weiteres wird folgen.

Bedienung:
Fahrt neben die Paletten und dann mit [R] das laden starten.
Achtet aber darauf, dass ihr auch dir richtigen Palettenart ausgewählt habt.
Die Paletten liegen dann wie von Hand geladen auf der Ladefläche. 
Mit Gurten befestigen bevor ihr weiter fahrt, sonst rutscht das weg.
Ihr könnt die Entladeseite wählen und entladen.

Changelog 1.0.1.0
- Fehler für Baumwollrundballen auf Dedi behoben
- kleine Anpassung an Lade/Entlade Verhalten um der Fehlerhaften Anzeige durch die Giants Engine auf dem Dedi entgegenzuwirken

Changelog 1.2.0.0
- Fehlende Übersetzungen für Shop eingefügt.
- Umstellung auf eigene Bindings um Doppelbelegungen zu minimieren.
- Setzlingspaletten können jetzt mit Europlatten geladen werden.
- Neue Ladetyp für Überladene Europaletten wie z.B. die von KsAG oder Schaumann (geringere Ladekapazität).
- Ladeverhalten auf Automatisches aufladen aller Paletten in Reichweite umgebaut. Ein mal [R] und alles wird aufgeladen.
- Palette von Pioneer fällt jetzt unter Überladene Europaletten.

Changelog 1.2.1.0
- Verbesserte übersetzungen RU von nagor
- Übersetzung in IT von Markus33 [ITA]
- Übersetzungen in FR geklaut von Illegaler neuer Veröffentlichung meines Mods von BOB51160
- lua Fehler beim verkaufen nach abladen behoben
- Eigenes Mod Icon erstellt.

]]></de>
        <it>
            <![CDATA[Mod di base per l'utilizzo di mod con specializzazione caricamento automatico di pallet.

È possibile trovare un esempio di come deve essere incorporata la specializzazione nel caricamento automatico per pallet Strautmann SEK 802.
Attualmente sono possibili solo europallet standard, serbatoi per liquidi, pallet big bag e rotoballe di cotone, altri seguiranno.

Come si usa:
- Assicurati di aver selezionato il tipo di pallet corretto.
- Avvicinati ai pallet e poi col tasto [R] per caricare.
- I pallet sono quindi come caricati a mano sull'area di carico.
- Fissa il carico con le cinghie prima di guidare, altrimenti cascano a terra.
- Puoi scegliere il lato di scarico e scaricare col tasto I.

Changelog:
v1.0.1.0
- Risolto un bug per le balle rotonde di cotone su Dedi
- Piccolo aggiustamento al comportamento di carico/scarico per contrastare l'errata visualizzazione da parte del Giants Engine sul Dedi

v1.2.0.0
- Aggiunte traduzioni mancanti per il negozio.
- Passaggio alle proprie associazioni per ridurre al minimo le doppie assegnazioni.
- Ora è possibile caricare i pallet di alberello con l'impostazione Europallet.
- Nuovo tipo di caricamento per Europallet sovradimensionati come quelli di KsAG o Schaumann (capacità di carico ridotta).
- Il comportamento di caricamento è stato convertito in caricamento automatico di tutti i tipi di pallet a portata del raggio d'azione. Basta premere una volta il tasto [R] e tutto viene caricato.
- Il pallet Pioneer è ora caricabile con l'impostazione sovradimensionata.

v1.2.1.0
- Traduzione migliorata per RU di Nagor
- Aggiunta traduzione per IT da Markus33 [ITA]
- Aggiunte traduzioni per FR rubato dalla nuova versione illegale della mia mod di BOB51160
- Risolto bug lua durante la vendita dopo lo scarico
- Ho creato la mia icona mod
]]></it>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Mod de base pour l'utilisation de mods avec la spécialisation Pallet Autoload

Vous trouverez un exemple d'utilisation dans votre propre mod dans le Strautmann SEK 802 Pallet Autoload.
Actuellement, seules les palettes européennes par défaut, les réservoirs de liquide, les palettes bigbag et les balles carrées en coton sont possibles, d'autres suivront.

Comment utiliser:
Conduisez à côté des palettes, puis avec R, vous pouvez charger une palette après l'autre.
Assurez-vous d'avoir sélectionné le bon type de palette.
Les palettes sont alors comme chargées à la main sur la zone de chargement.
Fixez avec des sangles avant de conduire, sinon il tombe.
Vous pouvez choisir le côté de déchargement et le décharger.

Journal des modifications 1.0.1.0
- Erreur pour les balles carrées de coton sur Dedi résolue
- petite modification du comportement de chargement/déchargement pour lutter contre le mauvais affichage du moteur Giants dans Dedi

Journal des modifications 1.2.0.0
- Traductions manquantes ajoutées pour la boutique.
- Modifiez les liaisons en liaisons configurables pour minimiser la double utilisation.
- Les palettes de gaules peuvent maintenant être chargées avec le réglage de l'Europalette.
- Nouveau type de chargement pour les europalettes surdimensionnées comme celles de KsAG ou Schaumann (capacité de chargement moindre).
- Modifiez le chargement pour charger automatiquement tout ce qui est à portée en appuyant une fois sur [R].
- La palette Pioneer est maintenant chargeable avec le réglage surdimensionné.

Journal des modifications 1.2.1.0
- Traduction améliorée pour RU par Nagor
- Traduction ajoutée pour l'informatique par Markus33 [ITA]
- Traductions ajoutées pour FR volées de la nouvelle version illégale de mon mod par BOB51160
- Correction d'un bug lua lors de la vente après le déchargement
- Création de ma propre icône de mod
]]></fr>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>modIcon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_LOAD_PALLET">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_r"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_u"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="AL_UNLOAD">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_i"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="AL_LOAD_PALLET"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_LOADINGTYPE"/>
        <action name="AL_TOGGLE_TIPSIDE"/>
        <action name="AL_UNLOAD"/>
    </actions>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation"/>
</modDesc>